James E. McDonald papers, (1904-1997)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 2: General Research Files, 1953-1997
  - Series I: Research Files, 1953-1997
    - Unnamed (Kodak canister). (Box 53)